(Sheldon:)Granted not long,
but just deeply and well.
(Leonard:)I'm not surprised.
A well-known folk cure for insomnia...
(Leonard:)...is to break
into your neighbor's apartment and clean.
(Sheldon:)Sarcasm?
(Leonard:)You think?
(Sheldon:)Granted, my methods
may have been somewhat unorthodox...
...but the end result
will be a measurable enhancement...
...to Penny's quality of life.
You've convinced me, maybe we should
sneak in and shampoo her carpet.
- You don't think that crosses a line?
- Yes.
(Leonard:)For God's sake, Sheldon...
(Leonard:)...do I have to hold up a sarcasm sign
every time I open my mouth?
(Sheldon:)You have a sarcasm sign?
(Leonard:)No, I do not have a sarcasm sign.
You want some cereal?
I feel so good today, I'm gonna choose
from the low-fiber end of the shelf.
(Sheldon:)Hello, Honey Puffs.
PENNY:
Son of a bitch!
(Leonard:)Penny's up.
PENNY:
You sick, geeky bastards!
(Leonard:)How did she know it was us?